ARKADIUSZ ZYGAN

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+48 604 732 189
a.zygan@gmail.com
linkedin.com/in/arkadiusz-zygan
github.com/zyar3k
zyar3k.github.io/portfolio

PROFILE

I have always been close to the IT. I'm fascinated technological by development that has been taking place extremely dynamically over the last several years. In 2019 I decided join into IT World deeper, professionally. The idea of learning to code has been grown in me for several years. I have been systematically learning front-end programming for a year. I'm also interested in web application design, I try to keep up with trends. I completed a programming 9-month course supervised by an personal mentor -Bootcamp Web Developer Plus at Kodilla. In addition to the course I have completed interesting courses on the Udemy platform. I realize that a lot of work is ahead of me, which is why I train all the time and try to develop my skills. I focus on improving skills in JavaScript and React.

TECHNOLOGY

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- RWD
- Bootstrap
- Grid
- Flexbox
- AJAX
- API
- JavaScript ES5/ES6 z OOP
- ReactJs
- Redux
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB Stack

Tools

GIT, NPM, Yarn, Webpack, Jira, VS Code

HOBBY

- IT (programming, new technologies)
- Psychology (social, cognitive, NLP)
- Music (rap, soundtrack, jazz)
- Sports (football, handball)

SELECTED PROJECTS

BettyCraftDesigns - online shop

Zyar3k/online_shop_bcd--2022 (github.com)

Online store created from scratch. Application server and client. The ability to add products to your cart

Frontend:

react (cra), react-redux, react-thunk, axios

cors, express, mongoose, nodemon

cz@-app

Cz@-App (czat-appka.netlify.app)

Chat application from scratch - server and client

Used in project:

react, react-emoji, react-router-dom, socket.io-client, node-sass, cors, express, nodemon, socket.io

before I die

Zyar3k/before-i-die book-list (github.com)

A page with a list of recommended books. A list composed of lists recommended by 6 (or more) different sources. My help in controlling progress. Administration panel has been added. Database still to be updated

Used in project:

react (cra), react-router-dom, axios, node-sass, cors, express, mongoose

EXPERIENCE

Freelancer

England, Plymouth, 07.2016 - 04.2019

Self employment, cooperation with individual clients. First line of customer support. Supported industry:

- transport.

'ARO' Arkadiusz Zygan

Poland, southeastern part of the country 09.2008 - 06-2016

Self-employment - sales Representative, company-client cooperation. Industries served:

- construction,
- decorative,
- warehouse.

EDUCATION

Jan Kochanowski University in Kielce, Master's degree

Pedagogy Rehabilitation 10.2004 - 06.2009

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)"